1, 2, 3, 4
Baby, got me looking so crazy
빠져버리는 daydream
Got me feeling you, 넌 또 말해줄래
누가 내게 뭐래도 남들과는 달라 넌
Maybe you could be the one
날 믿어 한번 I'm not looking for just fun
Maybe I could be the one
Baby, 예민하대 나 lately
너 없이는 매일 매일이
재미없어 어쩌지
I just want you to call my phone right now
I just wanna hear you're mind
Cause I know what you like boy
You're my chemical hype boy
내 지난 날들은
눈 뜨면 잊는 꿈
Hype boy 너만 원해
Hype boy 내가 전해
And we can go high
말해봐 yeah 느껴봐 mm-mm
Take him to the sky
You know I hype you boy
눈을 감아
말해봐 yeah 느껴봐 mm-mm
Take him to the sky
You know I hype you boy
잠을 들려고 잠을 들려 해도
네 생각에 또 새벽 3시
알려줄 거야 They can't have you no more
봐봐 여기 내 이름 써있다고
누가 내게 뭐래도 남들과는 달라 넌
Maybe you could be the one
날 믿어 한번 I'm not looking for just fun
Maybe I could be the one
Baby, 예민하대 나 lately
너 없이는 매일매일이
재미없어 어쩌지
I just want you on my phone right now
I just wanna hear your mind
Cause I know what you like boy
You're mine
I can't make you like boy
내 지난 날들은
눈 뜨면 잊는 꿈
hype boy 너만 원해
Hype boy 내가 전해
You're mine, yeah we can make it right now
Yeah we can make it right now
We can go high
말해봐 예 느껴봐
Take him to sky
You know I hype you boy
눈을 감아
말해봐 예 느껴봐
Take him to sky
You know I hype you boy